Guide to the Samuel C. G. Watkins Autograph Collection
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
Samuel C. G. Watkins autograph collection
1890-1931
MS 698
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
1
(3 boxes)
Autograph collection of Dr. S. C. G. Watkins of Montclair, N.J. The collection consists mainly of letters (typed and holograph) to Watkins from various important persons in politics, industry, government, and the arts in the early 20th century.
Watkins, Samuel C. G., 1853-1942
Conditions Governing Access
The materials are open for research.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Gift of Edward Eberstadt, 1950.
Scope and Contents
Autograph collection of Dr. S. C. G. Watkins of Montclair, N.J. The collection consists mainly of letters (typed and holograph) to Watkins from various important persons in politics, industry, government, and the arts in the early 20th century.
Business; United States -- Politics and government; Great Britain; Europe; Autographs; Watkins, Samuel C. G., 1853-1942
- Inventory
  - Abbott, Lawrence Fraser, 1859-1933 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Acheson, Edward Campion, bp, 1858-1934 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Adam, Robert Borthwick, 1863-1940 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Adams, Alva Blanchard, 1875-1941 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Adams, Joseph Quincy, 1881-1946 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Adams, William H, 1862- (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Adler, Felix, 1851-1933 (2) (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Aldrich, Chester Holmes, 1871-1940 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Alfaro, Ricardo Joaquin, Pres. Panama, 1882- (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Al1en, Frank Gilman, 1874-1940 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Allen, Henry Justin, 1868-1950 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Allen, John Weston, 1872-1942 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Allenby, Edmund Henry Hynman Allenby, 1(st) viscount, 1861-1936 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Andrew, Abram Piatt, 1873-1936 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Angell, James Rowland, 1869-1949 (2) (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Angier, Roswell Parker, 1874-1946 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Armour, Jonathan Ogden, 1863-1927 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Arthur, Chester Alan, Pres. U.S, 1830-1886 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Athlone, Alexander Augustus Frederick William Alfred George Cambridge, 1(st) earl of, 1874- (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Ashurst, Henry Fountain, 1874-1962 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Astor, Nancy Witcher (Langhorne), viscountess, 1879-1964 (2) (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Astor, Waldorf Astor, 2nd viscount, 1879-1952 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Austin, Warren Robinson, 1877-1962 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Aydelotte, Frank, 1880-1956 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Bacharach, Isaac, 1870-1956 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Bacheller, Irving Addison, 1859-1950 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Bailby, Leon, 1868-1954 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Baird, David, 1881-1955 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Baker, George Fisher, 1840-1931 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Baker, George Pierce, 1866-1935 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Baker, Newton Diehl, 1871-1937 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Baldwin, Stanley Baldwin, 1(st) earl, 1867-1947 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Ball, Lewis Heisler, 1861-1932 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Ballard, Melvin J (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Barbour, Clarence Augustus, 1867-1937 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Barlow, Sir Montague, 1868- (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Barnum, Phineas Taylor, 1810-1891 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Barrows, David Prescott, 1873-1954 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Battlett, Murray, 1871-1949 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Barton, Bruce, 1886-1967 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Barton, Clara, 1821-1912 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Baruch, Bernard Mannes, 1870-1965 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Batterson, Walter E (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Bayard, Thomas Francis, 1868-1942 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Beach, Rex Ellingwood, 1877-1949 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Beard, Daniel Carter, 1850-1941 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Beatty, David Beatty, 1(st) earl, 1871-1936 (2) (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Beck, James Montgomery, 1861-1936 (2) (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Beck, William H (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Beecher, Henry Ward, 1813-1887 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Beedy, Carroll Lynwood, 1880-1947 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Beers, Henry Augustine, 1847-1926 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Begg, James Thomas, 1877- (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Bell, Bernard Iddings, 1886-1958 (2) (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Belmont, August, 1853-1924 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Benn, William Wedgewood, 1877-1960 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Bennett, Richard Bedford, 1870-1947 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Bernstorff Johann Heinrich Andreas Hermann Albrecht, graf von, 1862-1939 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Beveridge, Albert Jeremiah, 1862-1927 (2) (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Bigelow, Poultney, 1855-1954 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Bilbo, Theodore Gilmore, 1877-1947 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Bingham, Hiram, 1875-1956 (3) (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Bixby, William Kenney, 1857-1931 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Black, Hugh, 1868-1942 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Blackwood, Norman Jerome, 1866-1938 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Bok, Edward William, 1863-1930 (2) (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Booth, Ballington, 1859-1940 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Booth, Evangeline Cory, 1865-1950 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Booth, Maud Ballington (Charlesworth), 1865- (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Booth, W Bramwell, 1856-1929 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Borah, William Edgar, 1865-1940 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Borglum, John Gutzon de la Mothe, 1867-1941 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Bori, Lucrezia, 1888-1960 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Boring, Edwin Garrigues, 1886-1968 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Bowman, Isaiah, 1879-1950 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Bowman, John Gabbert, 1877-1962 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Bradford, Arthur Howe, 1883-1955 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Breckenridge, Lester Paige, 1858-1940 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Brewster, Ralph Owen, 1888- (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Briggs, LeBaron Russell, 1855-1934 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Brisbane, Arthur, 1864-1936 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Brooke, Charles Frederick Tucker, 1883-1946 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Brookhart, Smith Wildman, 1869-1944 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Brooks, Stratton Duluth, 1869-1949 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Broussard, Edwin Sidney, 1874-1934 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Brown, Arlo Ayres, 1883-1961 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Brown, Lytle, 1872-1951 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Brown, Walter Fogel, 1869 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Bryan, William Jennings, 1860-1925 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Buck, Clayton Douglass, 1890-1965 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Buckingham, Earle, 1887- (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Buckland, Edward Grant, 1866-1953 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Burgess, George Kimball, 1874-1932 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Burgess, Harry, 1872-1933 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Burton, Theodore Elijah, 1851-1929 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Butler, Nicholas Murray, 1862-1947 (3) (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Butler, Smedley Darlington, 1881-1940 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Butler, Thomas Stalker, 1855-1928 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Butler, William Morgan, 1861-1937 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Butterworth, William, 1864-1936 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Byng, Julian Hedworth George Byng, 1(st) viscount, 1862-1935 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Byrd, Harry Flood, 1887-1966 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Byrd, Richard Evelyn, 1888-1925 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Byrns, Joseph Wellington, 1869-1936 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Cadman, Samuel Parkes, 1864-1936 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Caetani, Gelasio, 1877-1934 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Calder, William Musgrave, 1869-1945 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Cambon, Jules Martin, 1845-1935 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Cameron, Ralph Henry, 1863-1953 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Campbell, Gerald, 1879-1964 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Cannon, Joseph Gurney, 1836-1926 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Capen, Samuel Paul, 1878-1956 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Capper, Arthur, 1865-1923 (2) (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Caraway, Thaddeus Horatius, 1871-1931 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Carey, Robert Davis, 1878-1937 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Catt, Carrie (Lane) Chapman, 1859-1947 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Chamberlain, Arthur Neville, 1869-1940 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Chamberlain, Austen, 1863-1937 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Chamberlin, Rollin Thomas, 1881-1948 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Chester, Colby Mitchell, 1844-1932 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Child, Richard Washburn, 1881-1935 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Choate, Joseph Hodges, 1832-1917, 1876-1968 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Chorley, Edward Clowes, 1865-1949 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Christianson, Theodore, 1883-1948 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Chrysler, Walter Percy, 1875-1940 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Church, Samuel Harden, 1858-1943 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Churchill, George Bosworth, 1866-1925 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Churchill, Winston Leonard Spencer, 1874-1965 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Clark, Edward Tracy, 1878-1935 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Clark, Joshua Reuben, 1871- (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Clark, William Henry, 1876- (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Clarkson, James S, 1842-1918 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Clay, John Cecil, 1875- (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Clemenceau, Georges Eugène Benjamin, 1841-1929 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Cleveland, Francis (Folsom), 1864-1947 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Cleveland, Grover, Pres. U.S., 1837-1908 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Cockran, William Bourke, 1854-1923 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Cody, Alpheus Sherwin, 1868-1959 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Coffin, Henry Sloane, 1877-1954 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Colby, Bainbridge, 1869-1950 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Cole, George M (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Compton, Karl Taylor, 1887-1954 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Comstock, Anthony, 1844-1915 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Conley, William Gustavus, 1866-1940 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Coolidge, Archibald Cary, 1866-1928 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Coolidge, Calvin, Pres. U.S., 1872-1933 (10) (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Coolidge, Grace Anna (Goodhue), 1879-1957 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Coolidge, John C (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Coolidge, Marcus Allen, 1865-1947 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Cooper, Myers Young, 1873-1958 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Cooper, Peter, 1791-1883 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Cooper, William Lee, 1878- (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Copeland, Royal Samuel, 1868-1938 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Cortelyou, George Bruce, 1862-1940 (2) (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Cotton, Joseph Potter, 1875-1931 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - DuPont, Irénée, 1871-1955 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Coughlin, Charles Edward, 1891- (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Courthope, Sir George Lloyd, 1877- (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Couzens, James, 1872-1936 (2) (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Cox, Channing Harris, 1879-1968 (2) (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Cram, Ralph Adams, 1863-1942 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Crandall, Rand Percy, 1865-1938 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Crane, Winthrop Murray, 1853-1920 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Creel, George, 1876-1953 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Crewe, Robert Offey Ashburton Crewe-Milnes, 1(st) marquis, 1858-1945 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Cross, Wilbur Lucius, 1862-1949 (3) (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Culbertson, William Smith, 1884-1966 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Cunningham, H A (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Curtis, Charles, 1860-1936 (2) (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Curtis, Cyrus Hermann Kotzschmar, 1850-1933 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Curzon, Francis Richard Henry Penn Curzon, viscount, 1884-1864 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Dana, Edward Salisbury, 1849-1935 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Daniels, Josephus, 1862-1948 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Darrow, Clarence Seward, 1857-1938 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Darwin, Leonard, 1850-1943 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Davey, Martin Luther, 1884-1946 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Davis, Dwight Filley, 1879-1945 (3) (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Davis, Harvey Nathaniel, 1881-1952 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Davis, James John, 1873-1947 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Davis, John William, 1873-1955 (4) (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Davison, Frederick Trubee, 1896- (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Dawes, Charles Gates, 1865-1951 (3) (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Dean, Bashford, 1867-1928 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Decker, Walter B (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - DeForest, Robert Weeks, 1848-1931 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Demarest, William Henry Steele, 1863-1956 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Denby, Edwin, 1870-1929 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Deneen, Charles Samuel, 1863-1940 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Depew, Chauncey Mitchell, 1834-1928 (2) (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Dern, George Henry, 1872-1936 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Dial, Nathaniel Barksdale, 1862-1940 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Dickens, Sir Henry Fielding, 1849-1933 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Dickinson, Lester Jesse, 1873-1968 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Dill, Clarence Cleveland, 1884- (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Dillon, Richard Charles, 1877-1966 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Dodd, William Edward, 1869-1940 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Dodge, Bayard, 1888- (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Dodge, Raymond, 1871-1942 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Doherty, Henry Latham, 1870-1939 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Donovan, William Joseph, 1883-1959 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Drew, John, 1853-1927 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Droege, John Albert, 1861-1961 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Duane, William J, 1887-1947 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Dulles, John Foster, 1888-1959 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - DuPont, Alfred I, d. 1935 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - DuPont, Francis V, 1894-1962 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Joffre, Joseph Jacques Césaire, 1880-1963 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - DuPont, Pierre Samuel, 1870-1954 (2) (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - DuPont, Thomas Coleman, 1863-1930 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Eastman, George, 1854-1932 (2) (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Eberhardt, Charles Christopher, 1871- (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Eckener, Hugo, 1868-1954 (3) (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Edge, Walter Evans, 1873-1956 (5) (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Edison, Thomas Alva, 1847-1931 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Edmonds, George Washington, 1864-1939 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Edmunds, George Franklin, 1828-1919 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Edwards, Clarence Ransom, 1860-1931 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Eiffel, Alexander Gustave, 1832-1923 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Eliot, Charles William, 1834-1926 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Elkins, Davis, 1876-1959 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Ellsworth, Lincoln B, 1880-1951 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Ely, Hanson Edward, 1867-1958 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Emerson, Frank Collins, 1882-1931 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Emerson, Louis Lincoln, 1863-1941 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Enright, Richard Edward, 1871-1953 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Erickson, John Edward, 1863-1946 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Erlanger, Abraham Lincoln, 1860-1930 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Ernst, Richard Pretlow, 1858-1934 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Everson, William Graham, 1879- (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Fairbairn, Archibald Macdonald Duff, 1883- (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Farrell, James Augustine, 1863- (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Faunce, William Herbert Perry, 1859-1930(2) (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Faversham, William, 1868-1940 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Fay, Sidney Bradshaw, 1876-1967 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Ferris, Woodbridge Nathan, 1853-1928 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Fess, Simeon Davison, 1861-1936 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Finley, John Huston, 1863-1940 (3) (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Firestone, Harvey Samuel, 1868-1938 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Fish, Hamilton, 1888- (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Fisher, Herbert Albert Laurens, 1865-1940 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Fisher, Irving, 1867-1947 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Fisher, John S, 1867-1940 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Fisher, Sir William Wordsworth, 1875- (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Fiske, Bradley Allen, 1854-1942 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Fletcher, Duncan Upshaw, 1859-1936 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Fletcher, Henry Prather, 1873-1959 (2) (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Foraker, Joseph Benson, 1846-1917 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Forbes-Robertson, Sir Johnston, 1853-1937 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Ford, Edsel Bryant, 1893-1943 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Fordney, Joseph Warren, 1853-1932 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Fort, Franklin William, 1880-1937 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Fosdick, Harry Emerson, 1878- (2) (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Fosdick, Raymond Blaine, 1883- (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - France, Joseph Irwin, 1873-1939 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Frank, Glenn, 1887-1940 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Frazier, Lynn Joseph, 1874-1947 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Frelinghuysen, Joseph Sherman, 1869-1948 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - French, Arthur E (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Fuller, Alvan Tufts, 1878-1958 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Fuller, Ben Hebard, 1870-1937 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Furniss, Edgar Stephenson, 1890-1966 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Galsworthy, John, 1867-1933 (2) (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Gardiner, William Tudor, 1892-1953 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Gardner, Oliver Max, 1882- (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Garfield, Harry Augustus, 1863 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Garfield, James Abram, Pres. U.S., 1831-1881 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Garfield, Lucretia (Randolph), 1832-1918 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Garvan, Francis Patrick, 1875-1937 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - George, William Reuben, 1866-1936 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Gerard, James Watson, 1867-1951 (2) (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Gibbons, Herbert Adams, 1880-1934 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Gibson, Hugh, 1883-1946 (2) (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Gifford, Walter Sherman, 1885-1966 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Gignilliat, Leigh Robinson, 1875-1952 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Gihon, Edward J (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Gilbert, Cass, 1859-1934 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Gildersleeve, Virginia Crocheron, 1877-1965 (2) (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Gillett, James Norris, 1860-1937 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Gimbel, Bernard F, 1885-1966 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Girdler, Tom Mercer, 1877-1965 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Gladstone, Herbert John Gladstone, 1(st) viscount, 1854 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Glass, Carter, 1858-1946 (2) (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Goethals, George Washington, 1858-1928 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Goff, Guy Despard, 1867-1933 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Gompers, Samuel, 1850-1924 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Good, James William, 1866-1929 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Gooding, Frank Robert, 1859-1928 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Goodnow, Frank Johnson, 1859-1939 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Goodrich, C E (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Goodspeed, Charles E, 1867-1950 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Grace, Eugene Gifford, 1876-1960 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Graham, William Johnson, 1872-1936 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Grant, Heber J, 1856-1945 (2) (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Grant, Percy Stickney, 1860-1927 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Grant, Ulysses Simpson, 1881-1968 (2) (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Graves, Bibb, 1873- (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Graves, Henry Solon, 1871-1951 (2) (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Green, Fred Warren, 1872-1936 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Green, William Raymond, 1856-1947 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Greene, Frank Lester, 1870-1930 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Greene, Jerome Davis, 1874-1959 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Grew, Joseph Clark, 1880-1965 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Grundy, Joseph Ridgeway, 1863-1961 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Guggenheim, Daniel, 1856-1930 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Hackett, James Keteltas, 1869-1926 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Hadley, Arthur Twining, 1856-1930 (2) (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Hale, Eugene, 1836-1918 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Hale, Fletcher, 1883-1931 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Hale, Frederick, 1874-1963 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Hammill, John, 1875-1936 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Hammond, Emily Vanderbilt (Sloane), 1874- (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Hammond, John Hays, 1855-1936 (2) (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Hanford, James Holly, 1882- (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Harbord, James Guthrie, 1866-1947 (2) (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Harding, Florence (Kling) DeWolfe, 1860-1924 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Harding, Warren Gamaliel, Pres. U.S., 1865-1923 (2) (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Harreld, John William, 1872-1950 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Harris, William Julius, 1868-1932 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Harrison, Benjamin, Pres. U.S., 1833-1901 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Harrison, Byron Patton, 1881-1941 (2) (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Harrison, George Leslie, 1887-1958 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Harrison, Leland, 1883-1951 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Hart, Albert Bushnell, 1854-1943 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Hart, Charles Calmer, 1878-1956 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Harvey, George Brinton McClellan, 1864-1928 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Hay, John, 1838-1905 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Hay, Mary Garrett, 1857-1928 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Hayes, Patrick Joseph, 1867-1938 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Hays, Will H, 1879-1954 (2) (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Heflin, James Thomas, 1869-1951 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Hendricks, Thomas Armstrong, 1871- (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Henson, Herbert Hensley, 1863-1947 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Herrick, Myron Timothy, 1854-1929 (3) (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Hibben, John Grier, 1861-1933 (3) (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Higgens, William L (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Hill, John Boynton Philip Clayton, 1879-1941 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Hilliard, Robert Cochrane, 1857-1927 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Hillquit, Morris, 1869-1933 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Hines, John Leonard, 1868- (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Hitchcock, Gilbert Monell, 1859-1934 (2) (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Hoare, Sir Samuel John Gurney, 1880-1959 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Hodges, Campbell Blackshear, 1881-1944 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Holbrook, Lucius Roy, 1875-1952 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Holloway, William Judson, 1888- (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Holmes, Elias Burton, 1870-1958 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Holmes, Oliver Wendell, 1809-1894 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Holt, Hamilton, 1872-1951 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Hooper, Lloyd P (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Hoover, Herbert Clark, Pres. U.S., 1874-1964 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Hope, Walter Ewing, 1879-1948 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Hopkins, Ernest Martin, 1877-1964 (2) (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Hornbeck, Stanley Kuhl, 1883-1966 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Houghton, Alanson Bigelow, 1863-1941 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - House, Edward Mandell, 1858-1938 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Houston, David Franklin, 1866-1940 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Howard, Edgar, 1858-1951 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Howard, Esme William Howard, baron, 1863-1939 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Howard, John Tasker, 1890- (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Howard, Roy Wilson, 1883- (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Howell, Robert Beecher, 1864-1933 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Hubbard, Elbert Hamilton, 1849-1912 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Hughes, Charles Evans, 1862-1948 (5) (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Hughes, Charles Frederick, 1866-1934 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Hull, Cordell, 1871-1955 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Hull, Morton Denison, 1867-1937 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Hurley, Edward Nash, 1864-1933 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Hurley, Patrick Jay, 1883-1963 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Huston, Claudius Hart, 1876-1952 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Hutchins, Robert Maynard, 1899- (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Insull, Samuel, 1859-1938 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Ironside, Edmund (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Jacks, Lawrence Pearsall, 1860- (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Jacobs, Thornwell, 1877-1956 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Jahncke, Ernest Lee, 1880-1960 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Jardine, William M, 1879-1955 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Jaspar, Henri, 1870-1939 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Jefferson, Joseph, 1829-1905 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Joffre, Joseph Jacques Césaire, 1852-1931 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Johnson, Hewlett, 1874-1966 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Johnson, Hiram Warren, 1866-1945 (2) (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Johnson, Nelson Trusler, 1887-1954 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Jones, Andrieus Aristieus, 1862-1927 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Jones, Hilary Pollard, 1863-1938 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Jones, Wesley Lively, 1863-1932 (4) (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Jordan, David Starr, 1851-1931 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Joynson-Hicks, Sir Wiliam, 1865- (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Judd, Lawrence McCully, 1887-1968 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Kaltenborn, Hans von, 1878-1965 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Kay, H George (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Kean, Hamilton Fish, 1862-1941 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Kean, John, 1852-1914 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Kellogg, Frank Billings, 1856-1937 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Kendrick, John Benjamin, 1857-1933 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Kennedy, Robert Morris, 1867-1946 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Kenyon, William Squire, 1869-1933 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Keyes, Henry Wilder, 1863-1938 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Kidde, Walter, 1877-1943 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - King, William Henry, 1863-1949 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - King, William Lyon Mackenzie, 1874-1950 (2) (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Kirby, Thomas Ellis, 1846-1924 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Kirkland, James Hampton, 1859-1939 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Klein, Julius, 1886- (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Knox, William Franklin, 1874-1944 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Knox, Ronald Arbuthnott, 1888-1957 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Kohler, Kaufmann, 1843-1926 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Kohler, Walter Jodok, 1875-1940 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Kriege, Otto Edward, 1865- (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Krock, Arthur, 1886- (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Ladd, Edwin Fremont, 1859-1925 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - LaFollette, Philip Fox, 1897-1965 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - LaGuardia, Fiorello Henry, 1882-1947 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Lake, Everett John, 1871-1948 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Lamont, Thomas William, 1870-1948 (2) (Box 2, Folder 13)